(Sheldon:)I didn't punch him.
(Sheldon:)He turned around,
and I gave him
(Sheldon:)a Captain Kirk karate chop.
(Sheldon:)I'm not even sure
(Sheldon:)he knows I did it.
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon,
(Leonard:)I've got someone here who
might make you feel better.
(Stephen Hawking(on skype):)Hello, Sheldon.
Professor Hawking!
(Hawking:)I understand
(Hawking:)you're struggling
with professional jealousy.
(Sheldon:)Thanks, Leonard, now he's
not gonna think I'm cool.
(Hawking:)Don't worry,
I know how you feel.
(Hawking:)I have never won a Nobel Prize.
(Penny:)Oh, wow, that
doesn't seem fair.
(Leonard:)It's fine.
I've been on The Simpsons.
(Sheldon:)How do you deal with
the success of your colleagues?
(Hawking:)I remind myself
(Hawking:)every scientific advancement
is a victory.
Also, I was on Star Trek.
(Leonard:)Oh, it was a good one. He played
poker with Sir Isaac...
(Leonard:)You don't care.
(Hawking:)Don't waste your time
on jealousy,